As admirers of AKB-0048,
we left our home planet.
0048 rescued us from the DES,
an organization that forbids entertainment.
There's so many people.
Are these girls all auditioning too?
What a beautiful lady.
Yeah.
Nice to meet you.
I am AKB-0048 manager and producer,
Tsubasa Katagiri.
The manager?
You will be participating
in the 77th generation AKB-0048 audition.
Those who are selected will become trainees
and come with us to AKB-STAR,
the home of the Zero-Zero Stage.
Oh, AKB-STAR.
The song we'll assign you for the audition is
Beginner.
You will be required to learn your music
in multiple languages,
but the singing and dancing of Beginner
are your conditions for passing the audition.
Yeah, I just love that song!
That dance is hard.
Really hard.
Mm-hmm.
Beginner is actually the one song I'm good at.
The rest, not so much.
Hmm?
Listen carefully.
I told you singing and dancing
were the conditions for passing, correct?
Singing and dancing?
After this, the group of you will take a brief
but very important lesson.
Okay, okay!
Give it your best shot, everyone!
Here!
Huh?
That's close!
It's an Assault Mic Saver!
Huh?
Come on!
Practice, practice!
Who are you?
Sonata!
I'm going to audition!
Fine.
How do I get some closure?!
I understand why?
Okay, thank you so much!
Okay, I know.
Just do what I get was going for
Because of repository!
Huh?
Come on, practice, practice!
Who are you?
Sonata, I'm going to audition!
Fine.
Our great effort becomes a song.
The tears we shed become stars.
The tears we can't reach you.
The dreams of our dreams
are far away.
The stars are the stars.
Let's go for trouble.
I will sing to the light.
You're lashing in love.
You're the most experienced vertical셀.
Like a knight.
You're the best CONEM Cuz Kidżar.
If you're is thepat逃avour,
I am facing potential olhar.
In my world's edible,
If you wake up your eyes,
Come know our wings.
But when you struggle,
Josh Miami
This is an idol!
Bless you!
In 10 days, AKB-0048 will perform a guerrilla concert on this planet.
By then, you must learn to flawlessly guard the successors.
What kind of concert requires combat?
You must only protect them.
If the enemy units are manned, you absolutely must not wound or kill them.
Now that I think of it, some of the members were fighting then, too.
Wait a second.
We're supposed to do that?
No, no, no, no, no way.
If you can't do it, you're finished here.
In order to perform on planets with entertainment bands, you have to be able to protect yourself.
Yes, this is no ordinary audition.
If you cannot pass this test, even if you became a member of Zero Zero, you would die.
Beginner is the last song of the concert.
Until the song is over, you must protect them.
That is your audition, girls.
I'm drenched in sweat.
Don't you think it's a little heavy for her to tell us we're going to die?
Jeez.
Yeah.
There's a trick to that.
First, you've got to flush out the rust.
Ouch!
Then, if you gradually decrease the flow of water...
Oh, I see.
Huh?
Dad?
Oh, don't use that one.
No matter what you do, that one only produces rust.
Oh, I'm too tired to be hungry.
Mmm.
Come on, eat up!
There, here!
An idol's body is her greatest asset.
No food means no strength.
So, come on, dig in!
Oh, my...
This is part of your training.
Eww, the rich flavor of the melting fat.
It's too much!
On a pretty strict diet.
Eww, we're sleeping in here?
It's very hard to relax in here, isn't it?
Oh, I'll never be able to go home.
I should write my will while I still can.
Kato, you always complain.
Starting today, it nicknames Grumbly Buddha.
Buddha?
It wasn't supposed to be like this.
Ori-nai...
I wanted to become an idol.
That's right.
Singing, dancing, shining.
I didn't want to crawl around like this
or get all sweaty fighting.
Ugh!
Shut up!
Huh?
Why don't you go home, then?
Are you going to be that half-hearted in your auditions?
It's ridiculous!
Cherry?
I'm sleeping in the lobby tonight.
No!
What's her problem?
Wait, Chiri!
Uh...
Nagisa!
Hey, wait!
Uh-uh!
Nagisa!
Hey, Nagisa!
Don't do this!
Just leave her alone!
Hey, quit it!
We wanted to make our dreams come true together!
She wasn't like that before!
Chiri's changed.
But she's...
The next question one!
Is...
This is how...
Our...
Our dad...
We've started this...
libraries
And chains on times...
Yes!
A bunch of Hallelujahs in the classroom
I just took over there...
But...
We were managed to be...
And...
The Constitution's determined...
And everything was already...
All these days about the system...
I went home!
Our whole family...
Oh, I'm lazy!
This is fucking great!
Your son埠…
What's their name?
Who is life doing!?
We ended our lessons a long time ago, didn't we?
Yeah. It's crazy.
The successors are still practicing this late.
How many times do we have to do this before you get it?
This staging has a quick changeover,
so you've got to move more smoothly.
We've been over this!
We know that.
You're the one who was offbeat.
What? They're fighting?
Focus! Focus!
We're all distracted.
The actual show's tomorrow, understand?
Let's calm down now.
I told you it's more like—
Please don't fight!
Hey! We're sorry!
I mean, it's just fighting's not a good idea, you know?
Right?
Sorry, sorry. We must have shocked you, but we're always like this.
Huh? Always?
Yeah.
We exchange opinions and point out all our mistakes to each other.
It's how we aim to put on the best performance ever.
But when we really get stuck, we—
Change your attitude, change your attitude, it will all work out!
So they weren't fighting.
Yeah, I guess that fighting and sharing ideas is kinda different.
Oh, it was wonderful. It really was.
Mm-hmm.
Over here!
Wait!
There's some other applicants!
Where are you going?
Hey, do you want to come with us? We're gonna complain to Tsubasa-san!
Tsubasa-san?
Yeah. We're gonna ask her to let us stop all this nonsense.
What?!
No one told us we'd have to fight in the audition!
That's right. The successors are singing, but we have to fight.
This isn't what I wanted. It's not fair!
But that's—
What are you talking about?! The successors are working really hard, you know!
It's not unfair at all!
Yuka!
Did you come here to be that half-hearted in your auditions?
Don't be a nuisance!
It's fine. Let's go together.
Yeah. What a goody-two-shoes.
I hate girls like that.
They think they're so great.
Yuka.
I said the same thing Thierry said.
I know...
I know Thierry is wrong, but...
But I...
I just...
I can't...
No!
No!!
Nores!!
It's starting to take shape.
Position change.
Chiari, take Yuka's position in the front.
Okay.
Here comes the next one.
Is something the matter, Chiari?
What's the matter? Are you not eating?
Uh, no.
At this rate, you'll definitely fail the audition.
They're starting to come in.
That's amazing.
All these people.
They're all here to see Zero Zero.
That's right.
There are plenty of people who want to see us despite the danger.
Never forget, that's who we are here for.
The only answer we can give to our fans' love
is to put on the best performance.
Mm-hmm.
Let's put our hearts into it and give them all our love!
Come on, you guys too!
Huh?
Thank you very much!
Oh, yes!
Thank you!
Yahoo!
Here we go!
Ready and...
We are always grateful!
Calmly, carefully, and correctly!
Are you doing what you want to do?
Yes, we are!
AKB-0048!
Hmm.
Wait.
Fuck!
Alright!
Though...
I'm feeling off my wrist right now.
Thank you.
Pam!
Cool!
Oh shit!
It's started.
It's rain!
Of all things...
Enemy attack!
In your position and set!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Here's还 free!
Let's go!
Ahh!
Zeroになるんだ
僕らは夢見てるさ
Ahh!
How am I supposed to do this again?
Oh!
Really?
Æ?
Ahh!
claim
I can't! I can't do it!
Fail, fail, fail.
Another poor harvest.
Girls, it was strange.
It had only been a little over half a month since we left our planet.
Those girls, my friend.
Until then, we've been ordinary girls you'd expect to find anywhere.
But I felt the moment I couldn't continue being an ordinary girl anymore.
I'm sorry.
At this rate, you'll definitely feel the audition.
Can't add a glow when they feel an idol's aura.
I can't hit anything.
Megisa.
They're coming.
I'll stop them.
Huh? You can't do that by yourself.
I will.
I'll protect the concert.
That concert gave us and everyone else, everyone who was in that audience, our dreams.
And I want this audience to share that same dream we experienced.
Jenny!
Ah!
Oh!
oh
Churi? Churi!
Nagisa?
Chiri?
Am I... Am I alive?
Mm-hmm.
Paintballs?
Nagisa! Are you okay?
Chiri! Girls!
You're all right.
Okay, good work, ladies.
Tsubasa-san?
How can she be so lighthearted?
The concert was a great success.
Nicely played, girls.
Thank you.
You too.
Eternity.
Inside the ring.
We've been given a new word.
We must notify Tsubasa-sama.
Inside the ring.
We repaired enemy machines we captured. They were virtual enemies.
Huh?
What?
This planet doesn't have an entertainment ban.
There's no way I would have girls who just started their lessons handle a real battle.
You gotta be kidding me!
Wait, wait, wait!
I don't understand!
Oh my goodness!
You should know well by now. Battles with weapons only create sadness and hatred.
But despite that, you stood to face it instead of fleeing in order to protect our important stage.
And you were able to maintain the most important element of being a member of 0048.
A constant love for your friends, no matter what the situation is like.
Consequently, everyone remaining here has passed the audition.
All of you will now become AKB 0048 77th Generation Trainees.
Now, switch out your weapons for mics.
And join us in delivering our music to the galaxy!
Congratulations!
We did it!
Yeah!
Yay!
We did it!
Sorry.
What?
Unfortunately
You fully could be killed
Let it be
Even if you desire the flame wasostoivent.
This truth is changing.
Shikante planet אחד Oh.
The shelter in your eye was sphere attracted
to individual beings.
If they place in the heart.
If they sleep.
They will feel connected.
With the light through the塊
Just like the loved one
This is GHSI
That even during the years
ToON itself
It's still like a name
The type of Corbin
The time it's still
into each other
Who is running?
Do you know how many tears will it be?
Come home immediately! You can't come here!
You've gotta hustle! Hustle!
Knowing there's something more gets you going!